http://www.snowtrails.com/footer/privacy-policy

×
Go SkiingGo Skiing OverviewBuy NowHours &
Lift RatesSeason PassesEquipment RentalsLessonsGroup DiscountSkiing BlogsSkiing EventsGift CardsCOVID-19 Safe Season PlansBeginners AreaBeginners Area OverviewLessonsPackagesChildren’s ProgramsGift CardsCOVID-19 Safe Season PlansGo TubingGo Tubing OverviewBUY NOWGlow TubingHours & RatesFrequent QuestionsQuick DetailsWeekday Private Park RentalTubing BlogsTubing EventsGift CardsCOVID-19 Safe Season PlansSeasonal ClubsSeasonal Clubs OverviewBuy NowClub Pass OptionsBenefitsBecome A Club LeaderClub FormsClub Leader AccessCOVID-19 Safe Season PlansContact Us
×
Menu
(800) OHIO-SKI   |   Snow Report
Updated:12/10/20 11:27PMOpening Day: TBDPlease Note: Scheduled Power Outage... will have our phones and systems intermittent Friday, Dec. 11th. If all goes well, the Power Company will have service restored and we’ll be working to bring our technologies back online. In the meantime, please reach-out here for assistance SnowTrails.com/ContactUsOur first snowmaking campaign of this pre-season saw marginal weather with high humidity and temps not dipping as low as desired each night, limiting production. Temps are forecasted to trend upward throughout the remainder of this week, with the possibility for snowmaking to return Sunday night, so we hope to get back to it then. Keeping the snow in stock-piles for now is important to shield the layers of snow beneath the surface to reduce the impact of warm temps and wind.Thank you for staying-up with us and please know although Opening Day will be delayed for now, we want nothing more than to get things going just as soon as possible for you. Snow Trails typical Winter season runs December through mid-March. We'll look forward to great times ahead with you for our 60th Winter Season of 2020-'21! You can grab your Season Pass now and be ready for fresh air and fun on the slopes!Winter Employment - Apply Now to be part of our Snow Trails TeamLearn More - Latest Blogs and our COVID-19 Safe Season Plans Snow Trails Ski Shop>> Open with Pre-Season Sale Hours Office Hours:  Monday - Saturday 9AM - 4PM Questions? Please Contact UsFull Report        WEB CAMS × Go SkiingBuy NowHours &
Lift RatesSeason PassesEquipment RentalsLessonsGroup DiscountSkiing BlogsSkiing EventsGift CardsCOVID-19 Safe Season PlansBeginners AreaLessonsPackagesChildren’s ProgramsGift CardsCOVID-19 Safe Season PlansGo TubingBUY NOWGlow TubingHours & RatesFrequent QuestionsQuick DetailsWeekday Private Park RentalTubing BlogsTubing EventsGift CardsCOVID-19 Safe Season PlansSeasonal ClubsBuy NowClub Pass OptionsBenefitsBecome A Club LeaderClub FormsClub Leader AccessCOVID-19 Safe Season PlansContact Us
PRIVACY POLICY & Terms of UsePRIVACY POLICYSnow Trails is very concerned for your sense of privacy and security while on our site as well as with respect to how we care for your information. The following is our privacy pledge to you and deals with the following issues:SECURITYThe importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our Guests is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information the Snow Trails site can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk.Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. Snow Trails operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection. Snow Trails has security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. The security measures we use include a firewall, encryption, and short web page expiration times.The firewall is a combination of hardware and software that securely separates the Internet from our organization's internal web servers. They are designed to prevent unauthorized access to our web servers.Encryption is used whenever financial information, customer identification and passwords are transmitted between Snow Trails and financial institutions. We use an encryption tool called Pretty Good Privacy (PGP). It scrambles your information into an unreadable format called cyphertext, so that even if a third party were to intercept the message, the data would be unreadable. In addition, we use Verisign site certificates that provide a 128 bit SSL encryption for our e-commerce.In addition to the technically driven security measures, we also follow internal privacy procedures. In most cases our employees will see personal information only in aggregate. Employees see only those data they need to complete your sale. All credit card transactions are handled on separate secure servers. Only authorized employees have access to these servers and your personal information that resides on those servers.Remember to close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if your computer is accessible to others or if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe.INFORMATION COLLECTIONIn a few areas on our Web site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, process your order correctly, and if necessary, follow up with you before or after your visit. For instance, we want your e-mail address or phone number so that we can contact you if, due to unforeseen circumstances (problem with a sale, etc).From time to time we may ask questions, or we may use data collected for order processing, to better understand our customers' preferences. This information allows us to improve our products and services, and to offer you specially tailored deals when appropriate. While some of this information is optional, other items (e.g., information required to process an order) are not.We will request information from you when you:Register as a member on Snow Trails' website.Plan a Group trip to Snow Trails.Place an order with Snow Trails.Provide feedback in an online survey.Participate in a sweepstakes or other promotional offer.Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list.In each of these instances, we may ask for any of the following types of information: name, e-mail address, phone number, address, customer and trip preference information, customer ID and password, as well as other similar personal information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. If you don't want to receive promotional material or special offers from us, we ask that you tell us this in the section on communications preferences (opt out by un-checking the appropriate boxes). Please note that in the case of newsletters or mailing lists, you will be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time. Furthermore, if you need to change your profile and/or preferences, due (for instance) to a change of address, you will be able to make the change at any time.If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list.Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. With respect to Ad Servers: We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.COOKIESFor each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations.The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, but is NOT shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you'll find them at most major Web sites.Snow Trails has three primary uses for cookies. First, we use them to specify unique preferences. Secondly, we use cookies to track user trends and patterns. This helps us better understand and improve areas of the Snow Trails site that our users find valuable. Third, to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart - these cookies are DELETED after you leave our site.While these activities depend on the use of a cookie, visitors to the Snow Trails site always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the Snow Trails site will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies.INFORMATION USEDifferent information will be used for different purposes. Some personal information is required to process your order. For instance. we need to know your correct age, height, weight, foot size, skill level and gender for rental equipment use.We may also use personal account information to generate statistics and aggregate reports for internal use and for sharing with affiliates. These statistics and aggregate reports will not contain any personally identifiable information. Your identity is kept anonymous.Aggregate information may be used to design programs and promotions that we think would be of interest to an identified group of customers. For example, if an analysis of purchase data shows that 30% of our guests are intermediate skiers who rent equipment, we may want to develop a special rental/lesson program for them to test new gear.In addition we may use the detailed profiles in order to target special offers and promotions more effectively. Knowing more about you allows us to personalize the delivery of site content to you (at this time personalized content delivery will be via email) should you wish to receive offers from us. If we decide to use information collected for any purposes other than those identified we will contact you for your agreement.THE BENEFITS OF PROVIDING INFORMATIONKnowing more about you allows us to personalize the types of information we send to you. This means that you will probably receive less mail from us (unless of course you tell us you want everything), and what you do receive will be meaningful and not filled with a whole lot of information that does not apply to you.NON-USE AND DISCLOSUREWe do not and will not sell or rent users information to any entity outside of Snow Trails. Please remember that anything posted on our message boards becomes public information and you should exercise caution about disclosing personal information on those pages.Snow Trails reserve the right to cooperate with local, provincial, federal, and international officials in any investigation requiring either personal information (including any information provided on-line through www.SnowTrails.com or reports about lawful of unlawful user activity on this site.Snow Trails reserve the right to disclose any information in an individual's account:To satisfy any law, regulation, or government request.If such disclosure is necessary or appropriate to site operation.To protect the rights or property of www.SnowTrails.com and its users, sponsors, providers, licensers, or merchants.www.SnowTrails.com also reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time.CHANGING PROFILE AND OPTING OUTShould you not want to receive promotional material from us we ask that you tell us in the section on communications preferences (opt out by un-checking the appropriate boxes).We will also delete your name from the database upon your written request sent to us via email. When you register and your account is created, we will confirm your registration by sending an email to the address that you supplied to us. All future emails to your account will contain information on how to delete your name from our database. Please keep this email and follow the instructions exactly when requesting that your name be deleted from our database.CONTACTING CUSTOMERSSnow Trails reserve the right to decide if they will contact customers should we be required to disclose any personal information (as outlined in non-use and disclosure).CHILDREN'S PRIVACYSnow Trails is concerned about protecting the safety of the children who use our site. The Snow Trails site directed to a broad, general audience - comply with the terms of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. As such, we will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information on users under the age of 13, for the purposes of selling directly to these individuals without the consent of a parent to do so. Parents have the ability to control what, if any, Personal Information about their child may be disclosed to third parties, by regulating the actions and behavior of their children using the internet. For each visitor to our Kids Area, our Web server recognizes no information regarding the e-mail address. We collect no information on consumers who browse the Kids Area.Kid's Area members may be required in the future to give only a non-identifiable user name, and an email address for their parent or guardian. We do not sell or otherwise provide information from the Kids Area to outside companies. With respect to cookies:We do not set any additional cookies on the Kids Area visitors.We do not require any visitor to provide date of birth at registration, though we do ask for an age or birth date when applicable for pricing purposes (for instance, children and seniors qualify for discounts on lift tickets). U.S. federal law prohibits discrimination in public accommodations based on age, so when we send out information on our programs or passes we are required to treat all site members equally, regardless of age.PHOTOGRAPHY & CONTENTAll photography and written content is the property of Snow Trails and can not be duplicated or used for other promotional purposes without the written consent of Snow Trails.LEGAL LIABILITYUnder no circumstances, including, but not limited to, negligence, shall Snow Trails be liable for any direct, indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages, including, but not limited to, loss of data or profit, arising out of the use, or the inability to use, the materials on this site, even if Snow Trails or a Snow Trails authorized representative has been advised of the possibility of such damages. 3100 Possum Run RoadMansfield, Ohio 44903Phone: 800.OHIO.SKIContact UsHours of OperationBlogCalendarWeb CamsPhoto Gallery
ShopBUY NOW - Skiing/SnowboardingBUY NOW - TubingSeason PassesSnow Trails Ski ShopLift Tickets & RentalsChildren’s ProgramGift CardsDiscountsCorporate Partner ProgramExploreTrail MapArea LodgingEntertainmentFood & DrinksGet to Know Snow TrailsQuality Snow StandardsForms & WaiversPoLicyPrivacy PolicyResponsibility CodeFacility PoliciesPass & Ticket Terms and ConditionsAboutFree Brochure RequestMedia ResourcesWinter EmploymentSummer Event Facility RentalsJunior Race ProgramSki PatrolThe Adaptive Sports Connection Copyright © 2020 Snow Trails.
All rights reserved. Privacy PolicyUpdated:12/10/20 11:27PMOpening Day: TBDPlease Note: Scheduled Power Outage... will have our phones and systems intermittent Friday, Dec. 11th. If all goes well, the Power Company will have service restored and we’ll be working to bring our technologies back online. In the meantime, please reach-out here for assistance SnowTrails.com/ContactUsOur first snowmaking campaign of this pre-season saw marginal weather with high humidity and temps not dipping as low as desired each night, limiting production. Temps are forecasted to trend upward throughout the remainder of this week, with the possibility for snowmaking to return Sunday night, so we hope to get back to it then. Keeping the snow in stock-piles for now is important to shield the layers of snow beneath the surface to reduce the impact of warm temps and wind.Thank you for staying-up with us and please know although Opening Day will be delayed for now, we want nothing more than to get things going just as soon as possible for you. Snow Trails typical Winter season runs December through mid-March. We'll look forward to great times ahead with you for our 60th Winter Season of 2020-'21! You can grab your Season Pass now and be ready for fresh air and fun on the slopes!Winter Employment - Apply Now to be part of our Snow Trails TeamLearn More - Latest Blogs and our COVID-19 Safe Season Plans Snow Trails Ski Shop>> Open with Pre-Season Sale Hours Office Hours:  Monday - Saturday 9AM - 4PM Questions? Please Contact UsFull Report        WEB CAMS×
